export const quiz2 = {
    topic: 'CSS',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'The full form of CSS is:',
        choices: ['Cascading Style Sheets', 'Coloured Special Sheets', 'Colour and Style Sheets', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Cascading Style Sheets',
      },
      {
        question: 'How can we change the background color of an element?',
        choices: ['background-color', 'color', 'Both a and b', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'background-color',
      },
      {
        question:'In how many ways can CSS be written in?',
        choices: ['1','2','3','4'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '3',
      },
      {
        question: 'What type of CSS is generally recommended for designing large web pages?',
        choices: ['Inline', 'Internal', 'External', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'External',
      },
      {
        question: 'How can we select an element with a specific ID in CSS?',
        choices: ['#','.','^','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '#',
      },
      {
        question: 'How can we select an element with a specific Class in CSS?',
        choices: ['#','.','^','None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '.',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following is the correct way to select all h1 headers in a div element?',
        choices: ['div h1','div-h1','h1', 'None of the above '],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'div h1',
      },
      {
        question: 'We can make rounded borders around elements using which CSS element?',
        choices: ['border-collapse','border-round','border-radius', 'None of the above '],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'border-radius',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which CSS property is used to specify different border styles?',
        choices: ['border-style','border','Both a and b', 'None of the above '],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'border-style',
      },
      {
        question: 'Setting an inline-block in CSS requires which of the following properties?',
        choices: ['display','color','block', 'None of the above '],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'display',
      },
      
    ],
  }